Varun Vijay, manager of a private bank, who was missing from Patna's Kankarbagh police station area for the last three days, is
no more in this world.
You will get goosebumps after knowing this news.  Varun
Vijay had gone to attend his friend's child's birthday party with his family members in Ram Krishna Nagar area late on Sunday night.
After this he
left his wife and children in Kankarbagh police station area and disappeared.  When
Varun Vijay did not return till the next morning, his
wife lodged a missing report at the local police station.
Now Varun Vijay has been a
very popular face of Patna
on social media.  He has many friends
who are big names in Patna.  Varun Vijay
was the manager of ICIC Labour Bank's Kankarbagh
branch.  Now the dead body of Varun Vijay has been
found inside a well in a farm in Ber police station area.
You should first see the CCTV footage of
how when Varun Vijay was
not found in three days, the police woke up and when the
police woke up, the CCTV footage was examined.
During this, it was seen that Varun
Vijay had gone to Ber area on his scooter.  He parks the scooter
and is not seen after that.
Last night, when Patna Police was searching the area on the same basis,
they found Varun Vijay's
slippers.  The police
decided to wait till today i.e. Tuesday.  But meanwhile,
early in the morning, the villagers informed the police
that there was someone's dead body in the well and it was stinking.
When the police arrived and took out the body, it was
found that it was the body of the same Varun Vijay
who was missing for three days.  You should
see the visual CCTV footage and the pictures to see how a happy family was destroyed.
Varun Vijay's wife had
lodged a missing report at Kankarbagh police station and
after that the search for Varun Vijay started.
What is the crime graph in the capital Patna?  This needs no telling.  Now the
police is pointing its needle of suspicion towards murder, suicide, love triangle and
many other options.
But Varun is no longer in this world.
His family members are not in a position to say anything.
But his friends say that he was
very sociable.
He was acquainted with many important people of Patna and was
also very popular in the bank where he was posted.   In
such a situation, amidst the rising graph of crime, the
disappearance of a private bank manager in this manner
and finding his dead body in a well definitely
points towards some major mishap.  This also
shows that anything can happen in the complexities of this whole matter.
But now it will be interesting to see
what conclusion Patna Police gives in this case of murder or suicide.  At present,
Patna Police is not in a position to say anything.  The
forensic team has
recovered many things from the incident site.  Patna Police has
started investigating the case in its scientific manner.  But the one who has gone will never
return.  The rest
we and you can only hope for justice.  What do you think about the
deteriorating law and order situation in the rest of Bihar, the
wickets falling rapidly in the capital Patna, i.e. the
murders of people and the
increasing graph of crime in the entire Bihar
?  Please do tell us in the comment box.
While you are at it,
check out the CCTV footage of when Varun Vijay was last seen.
[music]